Aladdin Company Records Collection 1907-1989 (bulk 1940-1982)
Clarke Historical Library
- Aladdin Company Collection - Series #9, (Photographs and Films)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - Glenview,1952-1957 (Box 246, Folder 2718)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - Glenwood,undated (Box 246, Folder 2719)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - Goodrich,undated (Box 246, Folder 2720)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - The Grange,undated (Box 246, Folder 2721)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - Graystone,undated (Box 246, Folder 2722)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - Greenbriar,undated (Box 246, Folder 2723)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - Grenda,1960 (Box 246, Folder 2724)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - Groveland,undated (Box 246, Folder 2725)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - Highwood,undated (Box 246, Folder 2726)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - Hillsdale,undated (Box 246, Folder 2727)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - Hillsdale without garage,1962 (Box 246, Folder 2728)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - Holbrook,undated (Box 246, Folder 2729)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - Hollywood,undated (Box 246, Folder 2730)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - Holmes,undated (Box 246, Folder 2731)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - Houston,undated (Box 246, Folder 2732)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - Ingelwood, catalog #64, #560703-704,1959 (Box 246, Folder 2733)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - Iris,undated (Box 246, Folder 2734)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - Jasmine,undated (Box 246, Folder 2735)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - Kensington,undated (Box 246, Folder 2736)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - Kenton,undated (Box 246, Folder 2737)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - Kenwood,undated (Box 246, Folder 2738)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - Kimberly,1952-1957 (Box 246, Folder 2739)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - Kinsbury,undated (Box 246, Folder 2740)
  - Records, Construction Prints, Negatives - Unfiled postcards,undated (Box 247, Folder 2741)
  - Records, Construction Prints, Negatives - Unidentified,undated (Box 247, Folder 2742)
  - Records, Construction Prints, Negatives - Unidentified house c.1940?,1940 (Box 247, Folder 2743)
  - Records, Construction Prints, Negatives - Unidentified house – print negative (1950s ?),1950 (Box 247, Folder 2744)
  - Records, Construction Prints, Negatives - Unidentified house,1952-1957 (Box 247, Folder 2745)
  - Records, Construction Prints, Negatives - Unidentified house,1952-1957 (Box 247, Folder 2746)
  - Records, Construction Prints, Negatives - Unidentified house,1952-1957 (Box 247, Folder 2747)
  - Records, Construction Prints, Negatives - Unidentified house,1952-1957 (Box 247, Folder 2748)
  - Records, Construction Prints, Negatives - Unidentified house,1952-1957 (Box 247, Folder 2749)
  - Records, Construction Prints, Negatives - Unidentified house,1952-1957 (Box 247, Folder 2750)
  - Records, Construction Prints, Negatives - Unidentified house,1952-1957 (Box 247, Folder 2751)
  - Records, Construction Prints, Negatives - Unidentified house,1952-1957 (Box 247, Folder 2752)
  - Records, Construction Prints, Negatives - Unidentified house,1960 (Box 247, Folder 2753)
  - Records, Construction Prints, Negatives - Unidentified house,1960 (Box 247, Folder 2754)
  - Records, Construction Prints, Negatives - Unidentified house,1960 (Box 247, Folder 2755)
  - Records, Construction Prints, Negatives - Unidentified house,1960 (Box 247, Folder 2756)
  - Records, Construction Prints, Negatives - Unidentified house,1960 (Box 247, Folder 2757)
  - Records, Construction Prints, Negatives - Unidentified house,1960 (Box 247, Folder 2758)
  - Records, Construction Prints, Negatives - Unidentified house,1960 (Box 247, Folder 2759)
  - Records, Construction Prints, Negatives - Unidentified house,1960 (Box 247, Folder 2760)
  - Records, Construction Prints, Negatives - Unidentified house,1960 (Box 247, Folder 2761)
  - Records, Construction Prints, Negatives - Unidentified house,1960 (Box 247, Folder 2762)
  - Records, Construction Prints, Negatives - Unidentified house,undated (Box 247, Folder 2763)
  - Records, Construction Prints, Negatives - Unidentified & Miscellaneous (no model names),undated (Box 247, Folder 2764)
  - Records, Construction Prints, Negatives - Aladdin Victory Hutment, latrine, scrub deck, mock-up gable, pallets, recreation building, mill,1941-1945 (Box 247, Folder 2765)
  - Records, Construction Prints, Negatives - Military contracts. Pit latrine, naval armory recreation building, standard 5-man army hut, scrub deck – WWII,undated (Box 247, Folder 2766)
  - Records, Construction Prints, Negatives - Fort Brady, Sault St. Marie, MI. WWII. Kellogg Field, Battle Creek, MI. WWII,undated (Box 247, Folder 2767)
  - Records, Construction Prints, Negatives - Barracks construction WWII, Hutment WWII,undated (Box 247, Folder 2768)
  - Records, Construction Prints, Negatives - Construction,undated (Box 247, Folder 2769)
  - Records, Construction Prints, Negatives - MISC photos,undated (Box 247, Folder 2770)
  - Records, Construction Prints, Negatives - Aladdin Store, Muskegon, MI,1928 (Box 247, Folder 2771)
  - Records, Construction Prints, Negatives - “Aladdin's New B-I-Y System”, photos,1962 (Box 247, Folder 2772)
  - Records, Construction Prints, Negatives - Alaska-bound truck,undated (Box 247, Folder 2773)
  - Records, Construction Prints, Negatives - Bay Street House, Saginaw, MI. Steps of erection, negatives,undated (Box 247, Folder 2774)
  - Records, Construction Prints, Negatives - Bollingers Photographers, Charleston, W. Va. Unidentified houses,1937 (Box 247, Folder 2775)
  - Records, Construction Prints, Negatives - Bollinger Photographers, Charleston, W. Va. House #s 38722, 37855, 37873, 38089, 37842, 37722,1937-1938 (Box 247, Folder 2776)
  - Records, Construction Prints, Negatives - Hotel Doherty, Clare, MI. Cottage annex,1936 (Box 247, Folder 2777)
  - Records, Construction Prints, Negatives - Frost kitchen & bathroom,undated (Box 247, Folder 2778)
  - Records, Construction Prints, Negatives - Mill, Bay City, MI,undated (Box 247, Folder 2779)
  - Records, Construction Prints, Negatives - Hyde Park Wood Products, Cincinnati, OH,undated (Box 247, Folder 2780)
  - Records, Construction Prints, Negatives - Seattle logging (1958), garages & misc,1958, undated (Box 247, Folder 2781)
  - Records, Construction Prints, Negatives - Interiors of large colonial-style house, nd. (c.1930?) “...taken for the Smithsonian Institute or United States Museum in Washington D.C.”,undated (Box 247, Folder 2782)
  - Records, Construction Prints, Negatives - Experimental house #59036. Folder 1 of 2,undated (Box 247, Folder 2783)
  - Records, Construction Prints, Negatives - Experimental house #59036. Folder 2 of 2,undated (Box 247, Folder 2784)
  - Records, Construction Prints, Negatives - Experimental construction 1961 – see also Aladdin Problem Report (Administration, folders 13-16),1961 (Box 247, Folder 2785)
  - Records, Construction Prints, Negatives - Stewart. “Dendron House”; Russell, PA, 16345. Photos addressed to M. E. Frantz,1966 (Box 247, Folder 2786)
  - Records, Construction Prints, Negatives - Company Personnel c.1950 and earlier,1950, undated (Box 247, Folder 2787)
  - Records, Construction Prints, Negatives - Sovereign Personal Photos,undated (Box 247, Folder 2788)
  - Records, Construction Prints, Negatives - Sovereign Family recreation – old-timer (yacht) 1953. Yeager's Major (great dane) b. 1934,1934, 1953 (Box 247, Folder 2789)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - envelope: no. 1, April 25, 1952. Construction pictures of Melvin's house, excavation,1952 (Box 248, Folder 2790)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - envelope: no. 2, May 10, 1952. Construction pictures of Melvin's house, footings,1952 (Box 248, Folder 2791)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - envelope: no. 3, May 13, 1952. Construction pictures of Melvin's house, excavation,1952 (Box 248, Folder 2792)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - envelope: no. 4, May 14, 1952. Shipping pictures 1) truck shipments, 2) rail shipments, 3) packaging,1952 (Box 248, Folder 2793)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - envelope: no. 5, May 17, 1952. Construction pictures of Melvin's house, foundation,1952 (Box 248, Folder 2794)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - envelope: no. 6, May 19, 1952. Construction pictures of Melvin's house & Porter's, laying corner blocks,1952 (Box 248, Folder 2795)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - envelope: no. 7, May 20, 1952. McKinley house, see other folder for pictures,1952 (Box 248, Folder 2796)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - envelope: no. 8, May 21, 1952. Construction pictures of Melvin's house, wall plates, floor joints,1952 (Box 248, Folder 2797)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - envelope: no. 9, May 22, 1952. Construction pictures, of Melvin's house, floor joist, stair opening,1952 (Box 248, Folder 2798)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - envelope: empty,undated (Box 248, Folder 2799)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - envelope: no. 10, May 25, 1952. Construction pictures of Melvin's house, bridging,1952 (Box 248, Folder 2800)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - envelope: no. 11, May 26th & 27th, 1952. Construction pictures of Melvin's house, sub-floor,1952 (Box 248, Folder 2801)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - envelope: no. 12, May 27, 1952. McKinley house, see other folder for pictures,1952 (Box 248, Folder 2802)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - envelope: no. 13, May 15, 1952. McKinley house, Billy at McKinley house – see other folder for pictures,1952 (Box 248, Folder 2803)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - envelope: no. 14, June 2, 1952. Construction pictures of Melvin's house, outside walls,1952 (Box 248, Folder 2804)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - envelope: no. 15, June 1, 1952. See other folder for pictures,1952 (Box 248, Folder 2805)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - envelope: no. 16, June 3, 1952. Construction pictures of Melvin's house,1952 (Box 248, Folder 2806)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - envelope: no. 17, May 4, 1952. Construction pictures of Melvin's house, outside walls1952 (Box 248, Folder 2807)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - envelope: no. 18, June 7, 1952. Outside walls, interior partitions,1952 (Box 248, Folder 2808)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - envelope: no. 19, June 8, 1952. Construction pictures of Melvin's house, outside walls, ceiling joist, top plates, partitions,1952 (Box 248, Folder 2809)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - envelope: empty,undated (Box 248, Folder 2810)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - envelope: no. 20, May 4, 1952. Billy, see other folder for pictures,1952 (Box 248, Folder 2811)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - envelope: no. 21, June 13, 1952. Construction pictures of Melvin's house, outside wall sheathing,1952 (Box 248, Folder 2812)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - envelope: no. 22, June 16, 1952. Construction pictures of Melvin's house, outside wall sheathing, ceiling joist,1952 (Box 248, Folder 2813)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - envelope: no. 23, June 19, 1952. McKinley house, see other folder for pictures,1952 (Box 248, Folder 2814)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - envelope: no 24, June 29, 1952. Billy & McKinley house - #10 window, foundation,1952 (Box 248, Folder 2815)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - envelope: no 25, July 1, 1952. Construction pictures of Melvin's house,1952 (Box 248, Folder 2816)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - envelope: no. 26, July 2, 1952. Fence – McKinley house – see other folder for pictures,1952 (Box 248, Folder 2817)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - envelope: no. 27, July 2, 1952. Construction pictures of Melvin's house, rafters & gable studding,1952 (Box 248, Folder 2818)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - envelope: no. 28, July 4, 1952. Construction pictures of Melvin's house, roof sheathing,1952 (Box 248, Folder 2819)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - envelope: no. 29, July 10, 1952. Construction pictures of Melvin's house & Porter's house, roof sheathing, gable sheathing,1952 (Box 248, Folder 2820)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - envelope: empty,undated (Box 248, Folder 2821)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - envelope: no. 30, July 15, 1952. Construction pictures of Melvin's house, chimney construction,1952 (Box 248, Folder 2822)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - envelope: no. 31, July 28, 1952. Construction pictures of Melvin's house, eace & gable,1952 (Box 248, Folder 2823)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - envelope: no. 32, July 29, 1952. Construction pictures of Melvin's house, roofing,1952 (Box 248, Folder 2824)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - envelope: no. 33, July 30, 1952. Construction pictures of Melvin's house, roofing,1952 (Box 248, Folder 2825)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - envelope: no. 34, August 6, 1952. Construction pictures of Melvin's house, eave & gable, ginish, roofing,1952 (Box 248, Folder 2826)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - envelope: no. 35, August 7, 1952. Construction pictures of Melvin's house, roofing, vent, sack roofing,1952 (Box 248, Folder 2827)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - envelope: no. 36, August 19, 1952. Billy & McKinley house, see other folder for pictures,1952 (Box 248, Folder 2828)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - envelope: no 37, August 20, 1952. Construction pictures of Melvin's house, ridge roofing, window frames,1952 (Box 248, Folder 2829)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - envelope: no. 38, August 21, 1952. Construction pictures of Melvin's house, window frames,1952 (Box 248, Folder 2830)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - envelope: no. 39, August 22, 1952. Construction pictures of Melvin's house, window frames, cellar stairs,1952 (Box 248, Folder 2831)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - envelope: empty,undated (Box 248, Folder 2832)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - envelope: no. 40, August 27, 1952. Construction pictures of Melvin's house, outside wall finish,1952 (Box 248, Folder 2833)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - envelope: no. 41, August 28, 1952. Construction pictures of Melvin's house, siding, window frames,1952 (Box 248, Folder 2834)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - envelope: no. 43, September 4, 1952. Construction pictures of Melvin's house, outside wall finish – siding,1952 (Box 248, Folder 2835)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - envelope: no. 44, September 5, 1952. Construction pictures of Melvin's house, outside wall finish,1952 (Box 248, Folder 2836)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - envelope: no. 45, September 9, 1952. Construction pictures of Melvin's house, outside wall finish, metal corners, louvers,1952 (Box 248, Folder 2837)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - envelope: no. 46, September 10, 1952. Construction pictures of Melvin's house, blueprints, nail sketch,1952 (Box 248, Folder 2838)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - envelope: no. 47, September 17, 1952. Construction pictures of Melvin's house, exterior door frames, louvers,1952 (Box 248, Folder 2839)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - envelope: no. 48, September 8, 1952. Construction pictures of Melvin's house, siding, louvers,1952 (Box 248, Folder 2840)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - envelope: no. 49, September 20, 1952. Construction pictures of Melvin's house, window frames, door frames, freize board, soffit,1952 (Box 248, Folder 2841)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - envelope: empty,undated (Box 248, Folder 2842)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - envelope: no. 50, October 7, 1952. Construction pictures of Melvin's house, cellar stairs,1952 (Box 248, Folder 2843)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - envelope: no. 52, February 28, 1953. Construction pictures of Melvin's house, door trim,1953 (Box 248, Folder 2844)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - envelope: no. 51, February 24, 1953. Construction pictures of Melvin's house, window trim,1953 (Box 248, Folder 2845)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - envelope: no. 52, 1953. Construction pictures of Ward's house, louvers,1953 (Box 248, Folder 2846)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - envelope: no. 54, September 19, 1952. Construction pictures of Jack M's house, foundation hole, shovel work,1952 (Box 248, Folder 2847)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - envelope: no. 55, September 26, 1952. Construction pictures of Jack M's house, forming footings,1952 (Box 248, Folder 2848)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - envelope: no. 56, September 28, 1952. Construction pictures of Jack M's house, pouring footings, soil pipe,1952 (Box 248, Folder 2849)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - envelope: no. 57, October 4, 1952. Construction pictures of Jack M's house, completed foundation,1952 (Box 248, Folder 2850)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - envelope: no. 58, October 5, 1952. Construction pictures of Jack M's house, exterior walls, sheating,1952 (Box 248, Folder 2851)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - envelope: no. 59, October 3, 1952. Construction pictures of Jack M's house, completed foundation, first load materials,1952 (Box 248, Folder 2852)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - envelope: empty,undated (Box 248, Folder 2853)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - envelope: no. 60, October 11, 1952. Construction pictures of Jack M's house, building bee, applying sheathing, gable rafters, main rafters,1952 (Box 248, Folder 2854)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - envelope: no. 61, October 19, 1952. Construction pictures of Jack M's house, completed exterior sheathing, roof sheathing, gable ridge, main ridge,1952 (Box 248, Folder 2855)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - envelope: no. 62, October 25, 1952. Construction pictures of Jack M's house, applying valley flashing & roof shingles, window frames,1952 (Box 248, Folder 2856)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - envelope: no. 63, October 30, 1952. Construction pictures of Jack M's house, exterior frame, etc. - exterior of house,1952 (Box 248, Folder 2857)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - envelope: no. 64, 1953. Construction pictures of Jack M's house, corner blocking, cutting error, electrical boxes,1953 (Box 248, Folder 2858)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - envelope: no. 65, February 28, 1953. Construction pictures of Jack M's house, light boxes,1953 (Box 248, Folder 2859)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - envelope: no. 66, May 1953. Construction pictures of Bob Haggerty's house, foundation work,1953 (Box 248, Folder 2860)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - envelope: no. 67, January 4, 1953. Construction pictures of Bob Haggerty's house, floor joist,1953 (Box 248, Folder 2861)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - envelope: no. 68, June 25, 1953. Construction pictures of Bob Haggerty's house, outside walls,1953 (Box 248, Folder 2862)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - envelope: no. 69. Construction pictures of Barnes house, vacant lot, building lines, dredging, sewer tile, forming footings,undated (Box 248, Folder 2863)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - envelope: empty,undated (Box 248, Folder 2864)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - envelope: no. 70. Construction pictures of Barnes house, sandfill,undated (Box 248, Folder 2865)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - envelope: no. 71. Construction pictures of Barnes house, leveling, footings, poured footings, drain tile & crushed stone,undated (Box 248, Folder 2866)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - envelope: no. 72. Construction pictures of Barnes house, laying blocks,undated (Box 248, Folder 2867)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - envelope: no. 73. Construction pictures of Barnes house, laying block, laying glass block, bull-dozing,undated (Box 248, Folder 2868)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - envelope: no. 74. Construction pictures of Barnes house, squaring for foundation, marking for corner block, laying corner block,undated (Box 248, Folder 2869)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - envelope: no. 75. Construction pictures of Barnes house, leveling instrument, footing form, plastering outside wall,undated (Box 248, Folder 2870)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - envelope: no. 76. Construction pictures of Barnes house, plastering outside walls, crushed stone, tarring outside walls, basement window forming and making lintel, layer conductor tile,undated (Box 248, Folder 2871)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - envelope: no. 77, July 7, 1954. Construction pictures of Barnes house, conductor pipe, caved in walls, bull-dozing, first load, finish foundation, wall plates, floor joist, sub floor, wall construction,1954 (Box 248, Folder 2872)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - envelope: no. 78, July 14, 1954. Construction pictures of Barnes house, checking interior rough door openings, top plates, wall sheathing, ceiling joist,1954 (Box 248, Folder 2873)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - envelope: no. 79, July 22, 1954. Construction pictures of Barnes house, rafters, roof sheathing,1954 (Box 248, Folder 2874)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - envelope: empty,undated (Box 248, Folder 2875)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - envelope: no. 80, October. Construction pictures of Barnes house, plumbing – sewer tile,undated (Box 248, Folder 2876)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - envelope: no. 81, December 12, 1954 (Sunday). Construction pictures of Barnes house, copper plumbing, plumbing panel opening, bathroom fixtures supports, corner-rite, exterior finish of house,1954 (Box 248, Folder 2877)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - envelope: no. 82, September 3, 1954. Construction pictures of Barnes house – roofing,1954 (Box 248, Folder 2878)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - envelope: no. 83, January 9, 1955. Construction pictures of Barnes house, flooring,1955 (Box 248, Folder 2879)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - envelope: no. 84, January 15, 1955. Construction pictures of Barnes house, trimming large window,1955 (Box 248, Folder 2880)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - envelope: no. 85, January 24, 1955. Construction pictures of Barnes house, constructing by-passing sliding door, kitchen window, bathroom plywood floor,1955 (Box 248, Folder 2881)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - envelope: no. 86, February 7, 1955. Construction pictures of Barnes house, trimming door opening, applying lock & hinges, front entrance tile,1955 (Box 248, Folder 2882)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - envelope: no. 87, February 9, 1955. Construction on Barnes house, kitchen plywood flooring,1955 (Box 248, Folder 2883)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - envelope: no. 88, July 17, 1956. Catalina #2 – Rev. - BoV. - General Construction. Arthur Barry, Auburn, MI, order #560264,1956 (Box 248, Folder 2884)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - envelope: no. 89, July 17, 1956. Denver #1 – General roof rafters. Robert C. Trombley, Ann Arbor, MI, order #560394,1956 (Box 248, Folder 2885)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - envelope: empty,undated (Box 248, Folder 2886)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - envelope: no. 90, July 17, 1956. Ambassador, sub-flooring. Clifford Weingartz, Attica, MI, order #550610,1956 (Box 248, Folder 2887)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - envelope: no. 91, July 22, 1956. Ambassador #1 – hip roof framing sequence construction. Clifford Weingartz, Attica, MI, order #550610, #247 Printing and developing,1956 (Box 248, Folder 2888)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - envelope: no. 92, July 23, 1956. Ambassador #1 – hip roof framing sequence construction. Clifford Weingartz, Attica, MI, order #550610,1956 (Box 248, Folder 2889)
  - Records, Photographs and Films - envelope: no. 93, July 24th & 26th, 1956. Ambassador #1 – hip roof sheathing and applying roof shingles. Clifford Weingartz, Attica, MI, order #55061,1956 (Box 248, Folder 2890)